

PROFILE

I am a graduate of the University of Ibadan with a close to intermediate skill in python for Data Science Machine Learning and Data Analysis, not only have I built interest in this field, I have also worked on projects such as an Analysis of Nigeria's Covid19 data and participated in Data Science competitions such as Financial Inclusion in Africa and Insurance prediction on ZINDI.

I'm also an active member of Al+club University of Ibadan, Al Saturdays Ibadan and Developers student club University of Ibadan.

CONTACT

PHONE: 07055681047

ZINDI ACCOUNT: https://bit.ly/2X1DafL

TWITTER:

@dayomichael11

EMAIL:

abegunde.michael2@gmail.com

ORGANIZATIONS AND CLUBS

Al+ Club UI Data Science Nigeria Al Saturdays Ibadan StoryWithData

ABEGUNDE ADEDAYO MICHAEL

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN B.SC. GEOLOGY 2016–2020

Won the award for the most supportive finalist in Geology Department and also got the 'Most Dedicated Executive' Award while serving as the Financial Secretary of the student body in Geology Department.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FELLOW AT AI+CLUB UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN

March 2020 - Till Date

Led the organization to gathering data and building an interactive dashboard to aid the understanding of the spread of the Covid19 pandemic in Nigeria.

DATA ANALYST AT STORYWITHDATA

June 2020 - Till date

Successfully completed an analysis on the racial discrimination of blacks in the United States with a story telling visual.

ZINDI

January 2019 - Till Date

Successfully completed an Insurance Prediction, Air Quality Prediction and Financial Inclusion Challenge on Zindi in which I was amongst the Top 20% in all competitions.

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

